And you came with a card in your hand.
Are you the daughter of the lady that
gave me the card last time?
Aw, you're sweet. Where's your mom?
>> She's in Iran.
>> She's in Iran right now. She got
captured?
Sudan, can you help out the situation?
Aw, your mother is so sweet. Her mom
came to my show last year. She gave me a
card and I read the card and I opened
the card. I didn't read the card cuz
when I opened the card I realized she
put her number and she gave me her
address. So
now my stepdaughter showed up tonight.
So
good to see you, my love. Now, there's
another There's another letter.
And is this is from your mom, too?
Is it from both of you? Thank you from
International Organization.
Thank you. Oh my god, it's a book.
Dear Maz
Oh my god.
Tell your mom I love her so much I
licked her letter, okay?
Mommy.
They're such a beautiful family, yeah?
Make sure you come every year and bring
a card.
>> [applause]
>> Okay, I'll put it here. She's my whole
world.
I'm going to cry. I'm a very emotional
person. People don't believe me, but I'm
going to take this home. I swear to god
I'll take it before I go to bed I'm
going to read it, okay?
She has a message for me? In this In
this or is it separate? Oh, so you give
me the card and there's a message
verbally.
What is the message?
>> She doesn't like you.
>> She told me that she doesn't like me.
>> She
loves
>> that she loves me.
I was just going to read the card. Now
I'm going to have to read it and
masturbate.
>> [cheering]
>> Tell mom I said that. Was you?
Tell her that.
Sincerely,
Nicole, I take the candle off the table.
I'm sorry.
>> [applause]
>> I only got one shot in this situation.
I have to give it to mom here.
We have a GUY HERE FROM JAPAN.
HOW AMAZING IS THAT?
>> [applause]
>> THAT'S WONDERFUL, BUDDY. SO, UH what's
your name?
>> Dutaro.
>> Dutaro?
Dutaro.
I [\h__\h] it up the second time.
Say it loud.
>> Dutaro.
>> [\h__\h]
The Punjabi was easier in English.
Dutaro. Dutaro. Dutaro?
Dutaro.
He goes, "Yeah."
But you know what's crazy? You guys are
together?
>> No.
>> Then how do you know his name so well?
>> [laughter]
>> It takes a week to learn Dutaro. Dutaro?
Dutaro Dutaro Dutaro Dutaro Dutaro
Dutaro Dutaro.
You already knew.
So, Dutaro,
what are you doing in Bangalore? You
live here?
>> No, I'm living in Japan.
>> You live in Japan. You just came to see
my show from Japan?
Hold on a minute.
From Japan?
You came to see my show?
You know, in next week, I'M PERFORMING
IN JAPAN.
>> [applause]
>> HE DIDN'T KNOW.
HE'S LIKE, "I WASTED ALL MY MONEY."
>> [laughter]
>> You know what I love? Of the whole
world, you chose India to come and see
the show.
That's very cool, man.
>> [applause]
>> Dutaro is my special guest tonight.
This is so incredible. He came from
Japan TO SEE HOLD ON. HOLD ON.
LET ME SAY THIS. HEY, YOU GUYS. YEAH,
YEAH.
THIS GUY FLEW FROM JAPAN
TO SEE ME. HE GOT TIME.
YOU LIVE RIGHT UP THE STREET.
YOU BROKE.
>> [applause]
>> YOU BROKE.
HE FROM JAPAN TO SEE ME. IF YOU ARE
LATE.
BELLA, thank you for coming by yourself.
That makes me very happy. That's so
nice. What do you do? Are you a dancer?
That bag is not for
>> [laughter]
>> Really?
Radiology?
In the radiology center, you strip?
That's so fun.
Can I come there and take a picture?
I would love for you to do my x-ray.
You'll find something amazing.
And and are you single?
>> I'm a recent widow.
>> You're actually you're you're you're a
recent widow.
Aw.
Give her a big round of applause for
coming out and and laugh.
WOW.
>> [applause]
>> I WAS LISTENING to you and it's helped
me feel better about
>> Aw, my love. You're so sweet. I feel
really guilty about the stripper joke I
made about you.
I take it back.
Aw, Bella.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> You're very sweet. I love you. I really
love you and I wish you such an amazing
rest of your life. Yeah, because you
never know what's going to [applause]
happen.
And I want you to live every moment to
the fullest. Uh you made my night. And
and uh the fact that somebody is going
through such a hard time and and they
come to watch comedy, uh it's very
special. You're so young, you're so
beautiful. You should go out there and
meet people and find love and have live
life every day knowing that it's not a
long journey. We're all going to go to
the same place as your husband and where
my dad is and everybody else who's lost
a loved one. They know life is fast. So,
let's live it today cuz that's going to
make them happy. Yeah?
>> [applause]
>> Any other widows in the audience?
>> [laughter]
>> I have a huge widow following.
What is the word for a man who loses his
wife? I- I- If a woman is a widow, what
is a man?
A widower? A man who loses his wife is a
widower?
I didn't know that. You know why? Cuz
men never complain when THEIR WIFE DIES.
UH OH, that's so So, you What did you
say? You got some gods to protect me?
Oh, thank you.
Mahadev?
Uh-huh. And it That's Okay. And what god
is that?
Wealth? God is of wealth? And this is in
what religion?
Hindu. Oh, that's so beautiful. But I am
into uh Allahu Akbar.
If I say Allahu Akbar five times, more
people show up.
I don't know if they're coming for
comedy or jihad. I'm not sure.
And and and how many gods you have?
So many?
Oh, you're so lucky.
That's why Indians are so many and
they're so blessed.
That's why Indians
>> [cheering]
>> OH MY GOD.
YES, they talk to one god, he's busy.
Okay, no problem. I talk to another god.
Excuse me, god number five.
I need you right now. You're busy? I
don't give a [\h__\h] I go for another god.
God number 23, are you here?
Oh, thank you very much.
You know,
my religion, one god.
AND HE'S ALWAYS BUSY.
I'M REALLY HAPPY AND YOU BROUGHT ME MORE
GIFTS.
Oh my god.
You are so sweet.
To Max, for the funniest judge of all
things.
Funny you
verdict. I cannot Is this in Is this in
a Hindu?
Oh, wow, there's three different things
here. That's so sweet. Your mom sent
this to me?
Yes? Is it a big dildo?
I don't know. Maybe there's a god of
dildos. Okay, Max, I'm eating in front
of everybody.
Are you trying to embarrass me in front
of everybody?
You sure?
Okay, I open this, but if it's some
funny joke
What do you make this very Oh my god,
it's so beautiful.
>> Lady Justice, so my mom believes you
have done justice to all the Indians by
doing Nach Baliye.
>> Oh my god, that is so beautiful. Oh,
that's very sweet.
>> [applause]
>> This is why I love you. Any Anyone here
from Pakistan?
Oh, nice. Do you guys have any gifts for
me?
Hi. You you you shaved your head?
Or is it for a medical reasons?
Yes. How are you feeling now?
>> Fine.
>> Fine. What's your name?
>> Aijohn.
>> Aijohn. First of all, nice to meet you.
Second of all, I'm so happy you're here.
Third of all, look at that smile. And
let me tell you something. I admire you
for
coming out
>> [applause]
>> with your head shaved
with so much confidence. Yeah?
>> [applause]
>> To come watch the comedy show. If you
dealing with anything in your life, find
an excuse to laugh every single day and
release the tension. And I'm again,
thank you for being such an amazing
inspiration to all of us. Yeah?
To come out. I love you. And after the
show, come backstage and say hi to
[applause] me. Yeah? But don't bring
your friends. They're stupid. Just you.
No, the lady next to you is awesome. The
guy with the mustache, I'm scared of
him.
I'm going to choose one couple to bring
them on stage and I'm going to play this
game with them. This couple is going to
win the best gift they've ever won in
their life.
Which couple wants to come on stage?
Raise your hands. Okay, I got nothing
here.
>> [cheering]
>> I don't like you. Too much energy. This
one here, you want to come on stage?
These two are cute. Come. Come. You two
come. Come on stage. Go that way. GO
THAT WAY.
LOOK AT THIS BIG BOY. WHAT'S UP, MY MAN?
HOW YOU DOING, BUDDY? HI. Nice to meet
you.
Please, you can stay here. Yeah? And and
uh what's your name?
>> Mike.
>> Mike. And what's your name?
>> Corinne.
>> Um
Mike and Corinne. Um Mike, any secrets
that you uh have that she doesn't know?
Probably? Yeah? Good or bad?
>> Oh, it's all good secrets.
>> It's all good secrets?
Corinne.
Do you have any secrets? Anything that
you know that your husband doesn't know?
>> Just one.
>> Just one? What Wow.
What's his name?
Do you think this secret is going to be
a very like big news? Something that is
going to really like boom explode this
guy?
>> Boom.
>> Yeah?
>> Why? Cuz I'm Lebanese?
>> No, I just I think I think because size
matters. You know, I
>> [laughter]
>> Okay. Corinne,
tell this man
the secret that you have.
>> Okay, hold on.
>> Oh my god, don't take your clothes off.
There are kids in the audience. You're
going to take something out of your bag?
>> Yeah.
>> [music]
[cheering]
[music]
>> Aw, that's so beautiful, man. Mike Mike,
congratulations, my brother. And
congratulations to you. This lady is so
incredible. She wanted to reveal to her
husband that she's pregnant. And I have
a secret that I want to reveal to Mike.
It's my baby.
>> [applause]